const questions = [
  {
    question: "to bring (something)",
    answer: "motsutekuru",
    display: "もつてくる",
  },
  {
    question: "to give up, to quit",
    answer: "yameru",
    display: "やめる",
  },
  {
    question: "to draw, to paint",
    answer: "kaku",
    display: "かく",
  },
  {
    question: "to put, to set",
    answer: "tsukeru",
    display: "つける",
  },
  {
    question: "to reserve",
    answer: "yoyakusuru",
    display: "よやくする",
  },
  {
    question: "to practice",
    answer: "renshuusuru",
    display: "れんしゅうする",
  },
  {
    question: "to get together, to collect",
    answer: "atsumeru",
    display: "あつめる",
  },
  {
    question: "to fix, to repair",
    answer: "shuurisuru",
    display: "しゅうりする",
  },
  {
    question: "to present",
    answer: "shoukaisuru",
    display: "しょうかいする",
  },
  {
    question: "to move",
    answer: "ugoku",
    display: "うごく",
  },
  {
    question: "to take down, to put down",
    answer: "orosu",
    display: "おろす",
  },
  {
    question: "to hang, to suspend",
    answer: "kakeru",
    display: "かける",
  },
  {
    question: "to put (helmet, hat) on",
    answer: "kaburu",
    display: "かぶる",
  },
  {
    question: "to ask",
    answer: "kiku",
    display: "きく",
  },
  {
    question: "to touch",
    answer: "sawaru",
    display: "さわる",
  },
  {
    question: "to search, to examine",
    answer: "shiraberu",
    display: "しらべる",
  },
  {
    question: "to suit, to be convenient",
    answer: "tsugougaii",
    display: "つごうがいい",
  },
  {
    question: "to be inconvenient, not to suit",
    answer: "tsugougawarui",
    display: "つごうがわるい",
  },
  {
    question: "to stay, to put up",
    answer: "tomaru",
    display: "とまる",
  },
  {
    question: "to correct, to fix",
    answer: "naosu",
    display: "なおす",
  },
  {
    question: "to change (train, bus)",
    answer: "norikaeru",
    display: "のりかえる",
  },
  {
    question: "to turn (something)",
    answer: "mawasu",
    display: "まわす",
  },
  {
    question: "to polish",
    answer: "migaku",
    display: "みがく",
  },
  {
    question: "to welcome, to receive",
    answer: "mukaeru",
    display: "むかえる",
  },
  {
    question: "to be useful",
    answer: "yakunitatsu",
    display: "やくにたつ",
  },
  {
    question: "to cross, to go accross",
    answer: "wataru",
    display: "わたる",
  },
];
export default questions;
